

# Facundo Adrián Villafañe Soria

**\** +5491134477511

✓ favillafane@gmail.com

in /facundovillafane

AIRCRAFT DISPATCHER | TEACHER

#### **About Me**

I am a passionate professional about aviation and education, with experience as an aircraft dispatcher and university professor. In the aviation realm, I possess a deep understanding of regulations and operational procedures, ensuring safe and successful operations. As an educator, I am committed to inspiring and guiding students towards academic and professional excellence, integrating technological tools to prepare them for the challenges of the workforce.

#### **Skills**

#### **Technical**

- Weigth and Balance
- Amadeus GDS
- Go Now
- Radixx
- Office Suite

#### **Abilities**

- Communication skills
- Reliable and professional
- Organized
- Time Management
- Dedicated
- Motivated

# Languages

## Work Experience

Full Professor of Ticketing and Reservations for the
 University Technical Degree in Aeronautical Management.

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional 2023- Currently

I design classes, prepare materials, evaluate students, and teach them how to use reservation systems, as well as the fundamentals of pricing and revenue management.

Assistant Professor in Air Cargo and Mail Handling.
 2024- Currently

#### Aircraft Dispatcher

FlySeg S.A 2021- Currently

• Aircraft Dispatcher for Paranair

2021- Currently

Certified for weight and balance of CRJ-200 aircraft.

#### Ground Operations Coordinator

FlySeg S.A 2019- Currently

- Ground Operations Coordinator for Iberia/Level
  2022- Currently
- Delegated Instructor for Ground Operations Coordinator for JetSMART

2022- Currently

- Aircraft Dispatch Coordinator for Sky Airlines 2021- Currently
- Ground Operations Coordinator for JetSMART
  2019- Currently

# Facundo Adrián Villafañe Soria

**\** +5491134477511

✓ favillafane@gmail.com

in /facundovillafane

AIRCRAFT DISPATCHER | TEACHER

#### Courses

### **Induction Course for UTN**

#### **Career Teachers**

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional 2023-2024

#### **Pedagogical Tools for**

#### **Virtual Classes**

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional 2023

#### **Amadeus System**

Escuela de Turismo de Córdoba 2022-2023

#### Big Data / Data Analyst

Codo a Codo 2024

#### **International Aviation Law**

IATA 2020

### References

#### **Alberto Caceres**

FlySeg S.A / Operations Manager

- +5491168820635
- acaceres@securityflysec.com
- www.flyseg.com

#### Andrés Bermejo

UTN / Program Coordinator

- +5491148677500
- abermejo@frba.utn.edu.ar
- www.sceu.frba.utn.edu.ar

# Work Experience

Continued

#### Passenger Service Leader

FlySeg S.A 2018- 2018

• Passenger Service Agent

2018-2018

## **Education**

Aircraft Dispatch

AVEA 2018- 2019

Airline Administration and Management

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional 2020

Air Cargo Basics

ICAPA 2021

UX/UI Design

Coderhouse 2022

React Web Development

Coderhouse 2021 - 2022

Bachelor's Degree in Psychology

UCSE 2010 - 2018